Guide to the GW Hatchet records, 1904-2007 RG0114
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
GW Hatchet records
1904-2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. GW Hatchet. Office of the Editor
RG0114
62.75 Linear Feet
The GW Hatchet began in 1904, before that it was called the Weekly Columbian, before that the Columbian Call. The newspaper celebrated its 100th anniversary in 2004. Materials in this collection include a master set of microfilm of the student newspaper "Hatchet" from 1904 to 1989, photographs of Burton Sapin, Quigley's Pharmacy, Lloyd Elliott, Dr. Dennis O'leary, President and Nancy Reagan and other photos from the 1970 to 1980s.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from GW Hatchet Office.
Historical or Biographical Note
The GW Hatchet began in 1904, before that it was called the Weekly Columbian before that the Columbian Call. The newspaper celebrated its 100th anniversary in 2004.
When the idea for a campus newspaper surfaced in 1902, the university was not yet named for the first president, but was still called Columbian University. It was not yet located in Foggy Bottom, but instead occupied a few nondescript buildings at 15th and H Streets, N.W. The student body was not especially united by any great amount of college spirit. But Charles W. Needham, Columbian University's dynamic President, was a visionary with dreams of a new and greater University, and a campus newspaper was a step in the right direction. Realizing that the University needed a publication that would create new student interest and spirit, Jesse W. Barrett, a law student and the son of a Missouri country editor, suggested to President Needham that a university newspaper be founded. With Dr. Needham's encouragement, Barrett formed a partnership with Otho L. Ferris, a fellow law student from Iowa. Mr. Ferris became the publication's business manager, and "The Weekly Columbian" was launched. Two years later, the University's name was changed to The George Washington University and the newspaper took the name, The University Hatchet. The first issue of the "Hatchet" appeared on October 5, 1904, with the editors noting that the present time was a critical period in the life of the University: GW was endeavoring to plant itself in the front rank of educational institutions.
This note was written in 2005.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include a master set of microfilm of the student newspaper "Hatchet" from 1904 to 1989, photographs of Burton Sapin, Quigley's Pharmacy, Lloyd Elliott, Dr. Dennis O'leary, President and Nancy Reagan and other photos from the 1970 to 1980s. Also included are unbound and bound copies of the 1904-2005 Hatchet, campus posters, 1992-1997, intercollegiate newspaper association, football team entering the Tin Tabernacle in 1939, extra copies of the Hatchet, multiple photographs and negatives from their files. The materials range in date from 1904 to 2008.
Formerly RG#22.2
Collection Organization
Organized into eight series: Office files, Images, Newspapers, Newspapers and posters, Images and awards, Newspapers, Newspapers, and Images.
Photographs; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Football teams; Sports; Hatchet; Elliott, Lloyd H.; Sapin, Burton; George Washington University; O'Leary, Dennis; Reagan, Nancy; Quigley's Pharmacy (Washington, D.C.); Reagan, Ronald
- Office files, 1905-2005; RG0114 Series 1; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence, brochures, forms, press releases, invitations, programs, media kits, memorandums, flyers, business card, constitution, and a magnet. Also included are copies of "The GW Hatchet Alumni News" and a published scrapbook of the class of 1995. They range in date from 1905 to 2005. The materials concern subscriptions, solicitation of advertisements (paper and online), employment, scholarships, suspension of the charter, special issues, the Board of Editors, unpublished "Hatchet" letter to the editor, history, history, Professor Charles Puffenbarger, Jesse W. Barrett, and the James Haley controversy.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Student publications - Hatchet, 06/28/1984-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - Alumni News and Special Edition for Sept. 11, 2001, 03/12/1993-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - Class of 1995 scrapbook, 08/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - constitution, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - history, 10/06/1905-03/27/2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - history - James Haley controversy, 1936, 04/07/1936-04/27/1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student publications - Hatchet - history - paper "A History of the GW Hatchet, 1902-1995", 05/1995-02/26/2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Editorials by Fred Winfield Weitzel and letter from President Clloyd H. Marvin, 09/22/1931-01/27/1932; RG0054 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Images, 1970 ca. - 1980 ca.; RG0114 Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 1)
  This series contains photographs and negatives. These images cover the dates 1970 ca.- 1980 ca. Subjects include Burton Sapin, Quigley's Pharmacy, Lloyd Elliott, Dr. Dennis O'Leary, President Reagan and Nancy Reagan, Foggy Bottom Metro construction, Red Lion Row, Dick Gregory, various basketball players, the university yard and other campus scenes. The original numbering of the folders has been maintained.
  Formerly ACC#490; original folder numbers maintained
  - Burton M. Sapin, Dean of School of Public International Affiars, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clark, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Picture of Woodward and Lothrop, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - A Shot of the Credit Office, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Quigley's Pharmacy, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Man holding glass, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Sign that reads Credit, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - Barbar Remerse, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - Ellsberg Lecturing, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - A glove with a hand inside, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
  - Women dressed in Victorian Clothing, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Graduation, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.11)
  - George Calling, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.12)
  - Women doing African dance, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.13)
  - Sheet of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.14)
  - Man and Woman looking through book, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.15)
  - Man speaking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.16)
  - Woman and man talking, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.17)
  - Man pouring water on a woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.18)
  - People dancing, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.19)
  - Chorus link at GWU, 10/1977 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Shots of professors, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.21)
  - President Elliot, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.22)
  - Men performing Karate, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.23)
  - Maps of the District of Columbia, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.24)
  - A guy skate boarding, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.25)
  - Pictures of Art exhibit, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.26)
  - A woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.27)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.28)
  - Contact sheet of students, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.29)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - A woman, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.31)
  - Glen Matthew and David Juda, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.32)
  - Man playing a flute, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.33)
  - V. P. Smith, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.34)
  - Bill Smith, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.35)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.36)
  - Sleeves of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Zaleut, B, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sheet of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Man with both arms raised, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - People playing instruments, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Woman giving speech, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - Sleeve of negatives on the faculty senate, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.5)
  - Sleeve of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.6)
  - Statue outside of Marvin Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - Sleeve of negatives of student playing basketball, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - Students playing volleyball, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Man playing guitar, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Three men singing and playing guitars, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - A band, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.4)
  - A band, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.5)
  - Man in a robot suit, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.6)
  - Sleeve of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.7)
  - Sculpture outside of Hirshorn Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Sleeve of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Woman looking at artwork, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
  - Hirshorn Sculpture Garden, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
  - Hirshorn Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.5)
  - Sleeve of negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 8.6)
  - A GWU basketball player, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Bob Lindsay, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9.2)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.3)
  - Same man as in #3, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.4)
  - Tom Tate, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.5)
  - A young man, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.6)
  - People gathered on the street, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.7)
  - Man raising his hand, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.8)
  - People gathered on the street, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.9)
  - Dr. Dennis O'Leary, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Dire Straits, 09/15/79 (Box 1, Folder 9.11)
  - Man at podium at Martha's Marathon, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.12)
  - Space shuttle launch, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.13)
  - A band playing, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.14)
  - Drummer of a band, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.15)
  - A guitar player, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.16)
  - State Poster Child, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.17)
  - Sleeve of negatives - Daneatnon, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.18)
  - Woman holding posters, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.19)
  - Men marching in respect of Vietnam, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.2)
  - Man praying, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.21)
  - Negatives of Halloween Party, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.22)
  - Negatives of Halloween Party, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.23)
  - Two students dancing at the dancethon, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.24)
  - Students dancing at the dancethon, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.25)
  - Two students dancing at the dancethon, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.26)
  - Guys talking, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.27)
  - Fire Department Vehicle, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.28)
  - Student protestors, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.29)
  - Man giving speech, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.3)
  - Panel discussion, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.31)
  - People surrounding a man, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.32)
  - Man giving a speech, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.33)
  - A woman standing behind a microphone, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.34)
  - Man giving a speech, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.35)
  - President Reagan and Nancy Reagan, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.36)
  - Peter Jennings, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.37)
  - Lyn Nofsinger at press conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.38)
  - Man speaking at commencement, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.39)
  - Woman giving a speech, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.4)
  - Space shuttle launch, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.41)
  - Space shuttle launch, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.42)
  - People walking into GW Hospital Emergency Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.43)
  - People gathered around K street, undated (Box 1, Folder 9.44)
  - People eating in a food court, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.1)
  - A woman picking up a drink, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.2)
  - Dog catching frisbee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.1)
  - Dog catching frisbee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.2)
  - Man catching frisbee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.3)
  - Two men twirling a frisbee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.4)
  - Man doing tricks with frisbee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.5)
  - Negs. of frisbee festival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.6)
  - Negs. of frisbee festival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11.7)
  - Foggy bottom construction, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Neg. of foggy bottom construct, undated (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - A male on computer terminal, undated (Box 1, Folder 13.1)
  - Neg. of Stuard/Computer terminals, undated (Box 1, Folder 13.2)
  - Forensic Science Dept., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.3)
  - Chairman of Forensic Science Dept., undated (Box 1, Folder 13.4)
  - Two men sitting behind a table with pamphlets, undated (Box 1, Folder 14.1)
  - Man signing for School of Law, undated (Box 1, Folder 14.2)
  - Freshman banquet, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.3)
  - Students looking at table, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.4)
  - Neg of labor day festival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.5)
  - Neg of project visibility, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.6)
  - Freshman banquet, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.7)
  - Neg of Law Graduation Day, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.8)
  - Anti-NUC Seminar, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.9)
  - Neg of the fire in the Rat Hall, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14.1)
  - Four guys sitting at the head table, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Four guys sitting at the head table, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.2)
  - A man smiling, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.3)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.4)
  - GW USA Senate Meeting, 09/1979 (Box 1, Folder 15.5)
  - A man smiling, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.6)
  - A man smiling, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.7)
  - A man smiling, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.8)
  - Gov. Board Meeting, 09/79 (Box 1, Folder 15.9)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - A man, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.11)
  - Neg of a man, 09/79 (Box 1, Folder 15.12)
  - Neg of Howard Finbard, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.13)
  - Neg of Jon Katz, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.14)
  - Neg of Photo #8, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.15)
  - Neg of H. Graubard Bailey, undated (Box 1, Folder 15.16)
  - Neg of GW USA Senate Meeting, 09/1979 (Box 1, Folder 15.17)
  - Neg of Gov. Board Meeting, 09/1979 (Box 1, Folder 15.18)
  - Red Lion Row, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.1)
  - Rugby Club, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.2)
  - Man selling items on the street, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.3)
  - Mitchell Halloween, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16.4)
  - Robert Vdelsman, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.5)
  - Spider Web, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.6)
  - Red Lion Row, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.7)
  - Street vendors around GW, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.8)
  - Buildings, undated (Box 2, Folder 16.9)
  - University Mail Service, undated (Box 2, Folder 17.1)
  - Neg of University Mail Service, undated (Box 2, Folder 17.2)
  - Cashing, undated (Box 2, Folder 17.3)
  - Volleyball, 09/21/1979 (Box 2, Folder 18.1)
  - Volleyball, 09/21/1979 (Box 2, Folder 18.2)
  - Neg of GW volleyball vs GA Tech., 09/21/1979 (Box 2, Folder 18.3)
  - Yoav Horn, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.1)
  - Cyprus Ambassador Jacovides, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.2)
  - Ralph Nader, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.3)
  - Neg of Yoav Horn, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.4)
  - Neg of Jacovides, undated (Box 2, Folder 19.5)
  - Sign for Term Papers, undated (Box 2, Folder 20.1)
  - Kodak Paper, undated (Box 2, Folder 20.2)
  - Blood Drive, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21.1)
  - Boeing ALCM, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.2)
  - Martin Marietta, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.3)
  - Model of Solar Array, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.4)
  - Washington International College, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.5)
  - Line shot of Kitchen materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.6)
  - Student sitting on bench reading, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.7)
  - Folk life festival, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.8)
  - Man on stilts outside Air and Space Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.9)
  - Our Domestic Resurrection Circus, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.1)
  - Man Dressed in Patriotic Clothing, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.11)
  - People gathered around a building, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.12)
  - Marine Marathon, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.13)
  - Man playing with frisbee, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.14)
  - Two people in water in a little boat/raft, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.15)
  - Monkey, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.16)
  - Outside Cafe, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.17)
  - Two students holding skeleton dressed as Soviet hockey player, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.18)
  - Man playing flute, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.19)
  - Man fishing, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.2)
  - Marine Marathon, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.21)
  - Missile Show, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21.22)
  - Cadavers, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.23)
  - Misc, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.24)
  - Alternative Colleges, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.25)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.26)
  - Negative of blood drive, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21.27)
  - Negative of Bertani, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.28)
  - Negative of handicapped, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.29)
  - Negatives of Roaches - BTG, undated (Box 2, Folder 21.3)
  - Man working gadget, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.1)
  - Women's Pix, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.2)
  - Women's Pix, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.3)
  - Women's Pix, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.4)
  - Sheet of contact prints of student, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.5)
  - Sheet of contact prints of Governing Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.6)
  - Sheet of contact prints of Program Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.7)
  - Sheet of negatives of Liza White, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.8)
  - Negative of Liza White, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.9)
  - Negatives of #5, undated (Box 2, Folder 22.1)
  - Two South African Kids, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.1)
  - A woman, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.2)
  - A man standing outside of a restaurant, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.3)
  - Man sitting in chair, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.4)
  - A man named Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.5)
  - Man standing, posing next to a car, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.6)
  - The American flag, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.7)
  - Woman painting another woman's face, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.8)
  - Man playing instrument with a band behind, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.9)
  - Adams Morgan Day Festival, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.1)
  - An interior Decorated: Joyce Kozloff at Renwick Gallery, 08/15/1980-03/01/1981 (Box 2, Folder 23.11)
  - Sheet of contact prints of GW campus, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.12)
  - Registration Line, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.13)
  - Ancient Chinese Jade Necklace displayed at Freer Gallery of Art, 09/04/1980 (Box 2, Folder 23.14)
  - Student protestors, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.15)
  - Pres. Reagan, Nancy Reagan and Pres. Elliot, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.16)
  - Construction, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.17)
  - South African mother and son, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.18)
  - Woman doing gymnastic, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.19)
  - Dick Gregory, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.2)
  - Chevy Chase (movie promo), 1980 ca. (Box 2, Folder 23.21)
  - Adam Baldwin, Matt Dillion, Chris Makepeace (movie promo), 1980 ca. (Box 2, Folder 23.22)
  - Man on a motor cycle, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.23)
  - Man looking at gadget, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.24)
  - People at bar, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.25)
  - A man, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.26)
  - Fred Flinstone, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.27)
  - Landscape at Kings Domain, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.28)
  - Man, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.29)
  - Spandau Ballet - Chrysalis, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.3)
  - Dr. Dennis O' Leary, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.31)
  - Happy Land of Hanna Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.32)
  - Ferris Wheel, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.33)
  - Students in class, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.34)
  - A little boy doing math problem, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.35)
  - People on water roller coaster, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.36)
  - Sara Lee, Barry Andrews, Robert Fripp and Johnny Too-Bad (movie promo), undated (Box 2, Folder 23.37)
  - A woman, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.38)
  - A Man, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.39)
  - Photo of negative of men, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.4)
  - Photo of negative of men, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.41)
  - Photo of negative of a woman, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.42)
  - A woman smiling, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.43)
  - Photo of a man, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.44)
  - A GW basketball player, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.45)
  - Same print as #43, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.46)
  - Photo - negatives of a man, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.47)
  - Robert Jones, Professor of Religion, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.48)
  - Negatives of Lablance Devine Debates, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.49)
  - A Man Posing, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.5)
  - Photo of negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.51)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.52)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 23.53)
  - Keith Morris - GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.1)
  - Clyde Burwell-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.2)
  - Clyde Burwell-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.3)
  - A man, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.4)
  - Randy Click-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.5)
  - A man, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.6)
  - GW Basketball, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.7)
  - Clyde Burwell-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.8)
  - Keith Morris - GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.9)
  - Jim McCloskey-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.1)
  - Keith Morris-GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.11)
  - Coach - GWU Basketball, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.12)
  - Keith Morris - GWU Basketball Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 24.13)
  - Student outside watching a band playing, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.1)
  - Man playing a banjo, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.2)
  - Negative-photo of project visibility, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.3)
  - Negatives-photo of registration, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.4)
  - Man looking at art work, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.5)
  - Registration, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.6)
  - Registration, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.7)
  - Man pouring from a bottle, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.8)
  - Man dropping tray, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.9)
  - Man displaying a model, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.1)
  - Man, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.11)
  - Guitar player, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.12)
  - Rock singer, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.13)
  - Man speaking behind podium, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.14)
  - Washington Monument, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.15)
  - A bus, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.16)
  - A woman behind her door, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.17)
  - A guy playing video games, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.18)
  - Three guys, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.19)
  - Negatives of Basketball plays, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.2)
  - Girls playing soccer, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.21)
  - Students in classroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.22)
  - Sheet of negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.23)
  - Man playing video game, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.24)
  - Magazine, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 25.25)
  - Roller coaster, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.26)
  - Life at GW negatives - photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.27)
  - Contact prints on ralley, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.28)
  - Negatives of project visibility, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.29)
  - Negatives of registration, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.3)
  - Negatives of Basketball plays, undated (Box 2, Folder 25.31)
  - Contact sheets of the Latin Dance [1/2], 04/07/1977 (Box 2, Folder 26.1)
  - Contact sheets of the Latin Dance [1/2], 04/07/1977 (Box 2, Folder 26.2)
  - Two men and a woman, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.1)
  - Men and a woman sitting at conference table, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.2)
  - Men and a woman sitting at conference table, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.3)
  - A group in a classroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.4)
  - Man at podium, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.5)
  - Students participating in class, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.6)
  - Contact print of people [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 27.7)
  - Contact print of people [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 27.8)
  - Rob Shepard / Rich Reno, PB negatives 11/13, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.9)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.1)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.11)